Hallelujah!
Good Morning!
When I was coming, I saw our children.
They were rejoicing.
I asked them, "What is happening here?"
They said, "Today is Children's Day!"
The SCOAN Sunday Service
We want to salute you, children; we so much believe you are the leaders of tomorrow.
We salute you!
Thank you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Hallelujah!
I was looking round when you people were dancing.
I saw many people (dancing), whilst others were not.
You have to rejoice with those who are rejoicing.
The Bible says, if you fail to rejoice with those who rejoice, your day of rejoicing may be delayed.
Tell your neighbour.
If you fail to rejoice with those who are rejoicing, your day of rejoicing may delay.
I will not say more than that.
So this is why you see me - when I just see people dancing, I actually join them.
I'm not pretending; I really mean it.
If you are dancing now, I will join you.
So please, you have to do so.
Sometimes when we allow our feelings to take over us, our senses to take over us,
we begin to say, "Until it happens to me, it has not happened!"
"Until I feel it, until it happens to me, it has not happened!"
Those who are giving testimony - "Oh yes, they are healed!
But I have my own here - until I am healed!"
That is the voice of senses, the voice of feelings.
"Until it happens to me, it has not happened!"
Don't allow that; you are a child of God and you know what faith is.
You need to know His faithfulness and trustworthiness.
Trust and obey
For there's no other way
To be happy in Jesus
Than to trust and obey
So you are the one singing this.
That is the song; it is a common song.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You have to.
Overflow Congregation
You have seen God is reliable and the moment you see this happen, it causes your faith to grow.
It will spontaneously, side-by-side, grow.
That is your faith - you know, faith is natural.
With what you have seen today, the testimonies of others are meant to build your faith.
It is not just to, "Eh, eh..."
It is to build your faith.
Don't let unnecessary anxiety - being anxious for now and the future - to take over you.
These are the tools satan uses to trap us.
If satan does not want you to be here and you are here, he has a way of doing it.
It will take over your thoughts, your heart.
You will begin to say, "Ah, when will this happen to me?
When will I get healed? When will T.B. Joshua touch me?
I don't know. I have been to many places".
Whilst you are sitting down watching, your thoughts will be taken over by all this.
Anxious!
"What time?"
"I'm still feeling it."
"How much does the man want to collect? Do you think this can be free?"
These are the tools satan uses to trap us, to torture us, to capture us.
You will be sitting down whilst all this will be going on in your heart.
Don't be anxious.
That is why we are here.
"When? How?"
The SCOAN Sunday Service
When you are anxious of your now and future, God's time does not matter to you.
When you are anxious of your now and future, where the solution comes from does not matter
because of desperation.
Because of what? - Desperation.
You will not listen to what other people are saying, testimonies of others,
"No, until I give my testimony!"
That is the thought that will be going on in your heart.
"No!" - "Oh yes, it happened!" - "Until I give my testimony; until I see it!"
When people are saying, "Thank You, Jesus!",
you will be looking round, trying to see, "What happened?"
before you say, "Thank You, Jesus!"
You see people standing up, "What happened?"
They want to see what happened before they can say, "Thank You, Jesus!"
Are you with me?
You have to work on your heart, the state of your heart.
If it is not at its best, you are just wasting your time
because our heart is the contact point.
What is going on in your heart now?
Are you looking at my size, my stature, the way I talk?
Are you examining my words - the content or the grammar?
A lot of things - people keep busy. Many are here; many are not here.
You can see the church - everyone on the seat.
You will be very surprised that the person you see sitting down is standing.
You can be sitting and also what? - Standing.
Because you have two natures in one person.
Yours can be sitting and your divine nature standing.
Who is sitting?
Who is looking at me?
Hallelujah.
Right now, begin to cast your burden on God. He will care for you.
With Him, all things are possible.
Hallelujah.
Do you know God loves you?
How do you know? Can somebody stand up and tell me,
How do you know Jesus loves you and how do you know you love Jesus?
Can somebody?
Yes?
Because I receive emails: People say that wherever I face, I usually ask questions from.
Ok, yes?
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Ok, let's hear from you.
Because we wake up every day with the breath of life.
The issue of miracles.
You like miracles too much.
Can you see now? You wake up every day.
If you do not wake up, it does not mean Jesus does not love you.
It has to do with grace; grace allows you to wake up.
You said, "Because you wake up every day".
I said, "If you do not wake up, it does not mean Jesus does not love you".
He still loves you.
How do you know?
How do you know? You must tell us.
You wake up or you do not wake up - which is the greater love from Jesus?
You wake up is the greater love from Jesus.
Ahhh!
Can you see now?
You wake up or you do not wake up - which is the greatest love?
She said to wake up is the greatest love so she can continue her sin.
If Jesus sees that you continue this wrong thing and He calls you home, is that not a blessing?
Can't you know that this death is also a miracle?
Not all - but it is a miracle.
Death is a miracle; it is a blessing.
If the Lord realises you are a candidate of Heaven
and in a minute you may lose that Heaven, He may call you home.
Are you with me?
Tell your neighbour.
If you are a candidate of Heaven and in a minute you may lose that Heaven,
He will call you before that minute.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
What else again?
I know Jesus loves me because of what He did on the Cross for me.
You know that?
Did you read it or your heart told you this?
How do you know this?
First, I learned it before I started acting on it and then I got to know that the Word of God is true.
No one would die for you without knowing you but He did die on the Cross to save me.
Are you preaching?
Who are you?
I am Zelda; I am a child of God.
How do we know you are a child of God?
By my actions and by doing the Word of God.
We have not seen any action; how do we know this?
My heart.
Your heart - we can't see your heart.
Yes, we are listening.
Because God knows my heart.
How do we know what you are saying is from your heart and is not something you memorised?
Clap for her.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Yes?
Let's ask the old man.
The love of Jesus is evident in every activity we perform every day.
You cannot do anything without doing it in correspondence with His power and grace -
from breathing, seeing, walking and even talking.
We are not saying you should talk for us.
Who is Jesus to you?
How do you know Jesus loves you? How do we know that you love Jesus?
I know that I love Jesus because to a certain degree, I am living...
To a certain degree Jesus measured for you?
No.
That degree is the degree Jesus has measured that you should not go beyond that degree?
There is a certain limit...
...Jesus gave you?
No.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Ok.
Jesus is an everlasting Lover.
He loves you all through and gives you the chance to keep loving Him too.
But the measure of how I know how He knows is a spiritual factor; I am a human being.
Absolutely.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You are a human being?
Sure. I am not in the Spirit power with God.
But His worshippers must worship Him in Spirit and in truth.
So, it means, you are not a Christian.
Yes, absolutely.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Clap for baba.
We thank God you are able to tell us this.
Thank you, sir.
You are going to start from where baba said he is a human being and not a spirit.
Is that true of you?
Yes, Man of God.
That you are a human being?
I am a human being.
You are not a spirit?
Sir, we are two beings.
I asked, "Are you not a spirit?"
I am a spirit, living in the flesh.
Eh hen.
Yes, sir.
How do you live in the flesh?
I have a soul and I have flesh.
We know you have a soul; that is why you have to eat rice and beans.
Yes, Man of God.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
We know that.
Yes?
I know Jesus loves me because He died on the Cross of Calvary for my sake
and He still prays for me.
How do you realise this?
I realise that through Scriptures.
Through Scriptures. Yes?
I know I love Him; that is why I am here.
But there is no way we can know that what you are saying is true of you.
Christianity lies in the heart.
We know that.
I live my life for Him - reading the Scriptures day-by-day
and meditating on Him through the Word of God.
Ok. Thank you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Jesus loves me because I have committed a lot of sins and a lot of things happened to me.
There were things that were supposed to have killed me but I'm still existing today.
If not for Jesus, I would be a dead man by now.
He loves me - that is why I'm still existing.
For you not to have died, what is the reward to Jesus?
I have to serve Him and love Him back.
I have to serve Jesus truthfully and love Him back.
You have not been doing that.
Of course, sir.
Can you see, your living seems to be in vain.
Yes, sir.
What next? Do you want to die?
No, I don't want to die now.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Thank you, my brother. Clap for him.
He says he doesn't want to die. He still promises Jesus to do better.
The Lord will give you the strength.
Ok, thank you.
I know Jesus loves me because we are told that God's love, Jesus' love, is unconditional.
So, I know that God loves me and I love Him too.
You love Him too - very frank.
Yes, Man of God.
You said?
I love Jesus because I know He loves me and His love is unconditional - for everybody.
I partake - I thank God I partake in God's love because I am His child.
You have to work on your forgiveness.
Yes, sir.
I said, you need to work on your forgiveness.
Yes, Man of God.
Because you have to forgive this man.
Okay - yes, Man of God.
I want to see you.
My husband.
I will see you.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
Let's go to the other side.
You will answer this question: By what authority are you here today?
We see you in The SCOAN; we don't know if you were led by the Spirit
or you are here to see your Chairman or loved one or your loved one carried you to church today.
You are welcome.
Can you be able to tell us, by what authority are you here today?
By the special grace of God, I am here to fulfill the purpose of God
because before God created me, He knew I would be here today.
Ok. So, you know if it is Jesus, we don't lie against Jesus.
What you are saying now, I cannot dispute it.
Ok?
I'm here by God's authority to come to the Arena of Liberty.
I'm seeking for God's intervention in my life.
So God led me to this place by His authority.
If God does not intervene, what will happen?
If God did not intervene, I wouldn't be here and my life would go astray.
And if nothing happens today, what will happen?
By the fact that I am here - it means God has done something in my life.
Tell us, what has God done in your life now?
God has increased my faith by my being here
and whatever that brought me here, I can see that God is taking care of it.
Thank you.
Did you listen to her?
This is confession. But the belief in her heart is over to God.
You don't know what you are confessing is what you believe.
How do we know that what you are confessing is what you believe?
It wouldn't be visible but if I say it in confidence because it is coming from my heart,
and my actions change according to what I say,
then people will know that what I was saying was truthful.
But people listen to your voice.
It is difficult for them to be able to know who is talking and by what authority.
The confidence in me - I am directed and led by God.
Thank you. Any other?
I think I am here because of God's plan.
I believe that each and every plan we have is not our plan; it is God's plan.
God knows best.
I tried before; I didn't manage to come.
I think because it wasn't God's time.
It wasn't God's time.
This is God's time now?
It is God's time.
Thank you.
Viewers, you are there and we are here. We just want to awaken your spirit.
TT Mel Flowers
RV Robert Begier 15/06/2018